1670 Goldcliff Circle.wav
Absolutely, that's the best one for customers to reach me at..mp3
Definitely, that’s amazing to hear. I can’t believe that many searches! Yes, it’s making sense..mp3
filenames.txt
Hmm, not sure what other keywords. whatever you recommend.mp3
Hmm, not sure what other keywords... what do you recommend.mp3
I see, it’s all about getting in the door, huh Ok then, let's go ahead and get that application in. What do we do next.mp3
It's Walter Nelson. N as in Pneumonia..mp3
Just city and state.mp3
No, I haven't put in any application before. This is the first time I'm hearing about this opportunity. Let's make sure it gets done right!.mp3
Oh yes, I know them. They're the big names around here. I’ve always wanted to get ahead of them somehow..mp3
Oh, that sounds fantastic! I had no idea this was an option..mp3
Oh, that's wonderful news! And the price is really reasonable, especially with the discount.mp3
Sure thing, what do you need to know.mp3
Sure, it’s walter nelson at gmail.com..wav
That makes sense. I always wondered why I wasn’t getting found..mp3
That sounds great! I’m looking forward to seeing how it all comes together. Just let me know when the appointment is scheduled..mp3
That's a great price! And no contract Even better..mp3
Well, I'd say 10 miles is good. That’s where most of my customers come from anyway..mp3
Wow, only two I’m lucky you called!.mp3
Yep, that's me. Ready to make any decisions needed!.mp3
Yes, that's perfect. That's exactly how it should be..wav